<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-05T16:45:44-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">422parks.com</title><subtitle>Travel Guide to National Parks and Beyond</subtitle><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><entry><title type="html">Mammoth Lakes Travel Guide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Mammoth-Lakes-Travel-Guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mammoth Lakes Travel Guide" /><published>2021-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-07-01T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Mammoth-Lakes-Travel-Guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Mammoth-Lakes-Travel-Guide/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;why-you-may-want-to-visit-mammoth-lakes&quot;&gt;Why you may want to visit Mammoth Lakes?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Countless trails into Inyo National Forests and Sierra mountains&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Numerous tranquil lakes for water activities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ski resorts in the winter&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Afford and upscale hotels, restaurants, and cafes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Millions of people visit Yosemite every year. But few continues eastward to meet this little gem hidden in the Sierra Nevada mountains. Mammoth Lakes, Mono County is a ski town two hours away from the Yosemite National Park. Although having a population of ~8000, it is not your typical small town. What sets Mammoth Lakes apart is its high-class styles and afford prices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mammoth/Mono%20County2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Mono County, California&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Mono County, California

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;where-to-go&quot;&gt;Where to go&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best to visit Mammoth Lakes is to explore and do what you like. But here is a few suggestions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;mono-lake&quot;&gt;Mono Lake&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mono Lake is one of North America’s oldest lakes, formed at least 760,000 years ago. The snowpacks in nearby mountains melt and stream into this endorheic basin. With no outlet, Mono Lake is more salty than the sea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mammoth/Mono%20Lake.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Mono Lake, California&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Mono Lake, California

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rock-creek-lake-inyo-national-forest&quot;&gt;Rock Creek Lake (Inyo National Forest)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inyo National Forest covers 1.9 million acres of protected land with numerous lakes. It offers countless camp grounds and trails to explore the forest and the wilderness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mammoth/Rock%20Creek%20Lake.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Rock Creek Lake&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Rock Creek Lake

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mammoth/Inyo%20National%20Forest.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Inyo National Forest&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Inyo National Forest

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;lake-crowley&quot;&gt;Lake Crowley&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crowley Lake is a reservoir on the upper Owens River in southern Mono County, California. Facing east, you can see the snow peaks of the White Mountain in the background.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mammoth/Lake%20Crowley.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Lake Crowley&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Lake Crowley

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;stay&quot;&gt;Stay&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I stayed at Sierra Nevada Resort &amp;amp; Spa. For ~$100 during off-season, it offers 4-star hotel quality like the Westin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;eat--drink&quot;&gt;Eat &amp;amp; Drink&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out Black Velvet Coffee for your breakfast coffee. The quality of coffee is amazing! They offer seasonal and specialty coffees.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="City" /><summary type="html">A hidden gem in Eastern Sierra</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Ultimate Mendocino Weekend Travel Guide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Ultimate-Mendocino-Weekend-Travel-Guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ultimate Mendocino Weekend Travel Guide" /><published>2021-05-14T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Ultimate-Mendocino-Weekend-Travel-Guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Ultimate-Mendocino-Weekend-Travel-Guide/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;san-francisco-to-mendocino-road-trip-itinerary&quot;&gt;San Francisco to Mendocino Road Trip Itinerary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-1&quot;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start from SF on Highway 1&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stop at Sonoma Coast State Park for a quick hike and rest&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Continue to Point Arena Lighthouse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Arrive at Mendocino (afternoon) and explore the town&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-2&quot;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Go for a morning jog at Mendocino Headland State Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have breakfast at Good Life Cafe &amp;amp; Bakery&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Visit Russian Gulch State Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Point Cabrillo Lighthouse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Narrow River Redwoods State Park (afternoon)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;(Optional) Head to Anderson Valley for wine tasting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/d/embed?mid=1F9ED1ozXbjKvAYlP9tC8sURkvGvrNaR1&amp;amp;hl=en&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;480&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-details&quot;&gt;The Details&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-1-1&quot;&gt;Day 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mendocino is a small town with 894 people. Yet, it packs a punch in natural beauty and historical architecture. It is a perfect getaway from a weekend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;sonoma-coast-state-park&quot;&gt;Sonoma Coast State Park&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started my trip from San Francisco. After crossing the Golden Gate Bridge, head to the beautiful Highway 1. Continue driving north while enjoying the beautiful coastal view. &lt;strong&gt;Sonoma Coast State Park&lt;/strong&gt; is a perfect pit stop to rest and have a quick hike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/Sonoma%20Coast%20State%20Park.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Sonoma Coast State Park&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Sonoma Coast State Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;point-arena-lighthouse&quot;&gt;Point Arena Lighthouse&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, continue your trip on Highway 1 until you are near Point Arena. Bartolomé Ferrer, a Spanish captain, first recorded Point Arena in 1543. Point Arena is a narrow peninsula jutting around 1/2 mile (800 m) into the Pacific Ocean. This sandbar creates a natural hazard to navigation, and hence the need for a lighthouse and fog signal here. &lt;strong&gt;Point Arena Lighthouse&lt;/strong&gt; was constructed in 1870. Its brick and mortar tower featured ornate iron balcony supports and a large Keeper residence with enough space to house several families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/point%20arena%20lighthouse%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Point Arena Lighthouse&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Point Arena Lighthouse

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/point%20arena%20lighthouse%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Point Arena Lighthouse&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Point Arena Lighthouse

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are very close to Mendocino at this point. Continue driving for ~40 mins until you arrive at Mendocino. Check in at your hotel/Airbnb and explore the small town (if you still have energy).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-2-1&quot;&gt;Day 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;mendocino-headland-state-park&quot;&gt;Mendocino Headland State Park&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A visit to the &lt;strong&gt;Mendocino Headlands&lt;/strong&gt; is a must. You may come to see the spring wildflowers, enjoy a crisp and clear fall day, escape to a cool summer climate or witness the winter migration of grey whale. The park provides Mendocino with a buffer area that preserves the town’s historical presence. Photographers and painters frequently visit various parts of Mendocino Headlands enjoying and capturing the scenic wonders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/Mendocino%20Headlands%20State%20Park.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Mendocino Headlands State Park&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Mendocino Headlands State Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;breakfast-at-good-life-cafe--bakery&quot;&gt;Breakfast at Good Life Cafe &amp;amp; Bakery&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a handful of cafes in this small town. The one I recommend is &lt;strong&gt;Good Life Cafe &amp;amp; Bakery&lt;/strong&gt;. You don’t want to miss out on their almond croissants! It is so good. Even better, bring your coffee and breakfast to Mendocino Headlands State Park. Have your breakfast while enjoy the amazing view of the Pacific Ocean!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;point-cabrillo-lighthouse&quot;&gt;Point Cabrillo Lighthouse&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Point Cabrillo Lighthouse&lt;/strong&gt; was the highlight of my trip to Mendocino. In 1850, an opium-trading brig Frolic wrecked on a reef north of Point Cabrillo. By 1904, several ships had wrecked in this foggy region. Finally in 1906, a bill was passed in Senate to fund the construction of Point Cabrillo lighthouse.
A romantic option is to stay in one of the Keeper houses near the lighthouse. Rentals are managed by Mendocino Coast Reservations. You can call 707-937-5033 or email mcr@mendocinovacations.com to make your reservation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/point%20cabrillo%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Point Cabrillo Lighthouse&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Point Cabrillo Lighthouse

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mendocino/point%20cabrillo%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Point Cabrillo Lighthouse&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Point Cabrillo Lighthouse

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-home&quot;&gt;Heading Home&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are coming back to San Francisco, I highly recommend returning through &lt;strong&gt;Narrow River Redwoods State Park&lt;/strong&gt;. Instead of hearing the ocean waves crashing on Highway 1, you could enjoy the peace of a quiet Redwoods Forest. You have miles of giant redwood trees covering the sky. Only a glimpse of light comes through the opening. The magnificent view is on par of the more famous Redwood National Park. If you are a wine lover, there are many wineries in Anderson Valley after you exist &lt;strong&gt;Narrow River Redwoods State Park&lt;/strong&gt;. Some wineries require reservations in advanced but the tickets are very affordable.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="Parks" /><summary type="html">A perfect small town for a weekend getaway</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2 Day Travel Guide For Grand Canyon National Park</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2-Day-Travel-Guide-for-Grand-Canyon-National-Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2 Day Travel Guide For Grand Canyon National Park" /><published>2020-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2-Day-Travel-Guide-for-Grand-Canyon-National-Park</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2-Day-Travel-Guide-for-Grand-Canyon-National-Park/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-day-itinerary&quot;&gt;1 Day Itinerary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scenic Option (e.g. photos, easy trail):
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Watch sunrise at Mather Point&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Walk the Rim Trail between Marther Point and Yavapai Point&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Lunch break&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Drive the Desert View Drive to visit different vistas (afternoon)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Watch the sunset at Yavapai Point or Pipe Creek Vista&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Outdoor Option (e.g. trail, exercise):
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Bright Angel Trail&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-day-itinerary&quot;&gt;2 Day Itinerary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Watch sunrise at Yavapai Point&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete the other option (scenic or outdoor)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lunch break&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the shuttle bus to Hermits Rest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Grand Canyon is a unique place to visit. It is a place that makes men humble. It is a place that displays the grandeur of nature. It is a place that everyone should visit at least once in their lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/mather%20point%20grand%20canyon%20sunrise.webp&quot; alt=&quot;mather point grand canyon sunrise&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Sunrise at Mather Point

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the must-do activities is to watch the sunrise at the Grand Canyon National Park. It is a magic moment. The tips of the cliffs start to glow. As the sun rises, more and more of the canyon bathes in the orange light. The best locations to view sunrise are &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yaki Point&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Hopi Point&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you enjoy the sunrise at &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, walk towards &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;. It is an easy walk with paved trail. With the sun behind you, you get to see the fully glory of the Grand Canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/mather%20point%20sunrise.webp&quot; alt=&quot;mather point sunrise&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since you get up early to see the sunrise, you probably wake up early. Rest or take a nap. You can grab lunch at the General Store in &lt;strong&gt;Grand Canyon Market Plaza&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you visit Grand Canyon, don’t miss out the &lt;strong&gt;Desert View Drive&lt;/strong&gt;. Although Mather Point and Yavapai Point are the most convenient, there are plenty of unique view points along Desert View Drive. The best of them is &lt;strong&gt;Lipan Point&lt;/strong&gt;. You can see how the Colorado River has carved down the earth to form the Grand Canyon, of which you wouldn’t see from Mather or Yavapai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_lipan_point.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Lipan Point&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Lipan Point

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are staying the night, don’t miss out on the sunset. The best places to watch sunset are &lt;strong&gt;Lipan Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Hopi Point&lt;/strong&gt;. This will conclude your day at the Grand Canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have one more day at Grand Canyon, head to the &lt;strong&gt;Bright Angel Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt; on the next morning. Be sure to go there early as parking spots are limited. Bright Angel Trail takes you to the bottom of the canyon. Did I mention that Grand Canyon is one mile deep on average? It is a challenging trail for the average person. Depending on your conditions, you should decide when to head back. Remember, it takes twice as much time to climb up then to go down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on how far down you go on the Bright Angel Trail, it can take you an entire day. If you have time left, visit the west side of the South Rim. Take the shuttle bus to &lt;strong&gt;Hermits Rest&lt;/strong&gt; or walk the trail. You can appreciate how deep the Canyon is on your way to &lt;strong&gt;Trailview Overlook&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure words can describe the beauty of Grand Canyon. You have to go there to see it and experience it youself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For most people, it is probably enough to stay two nights and one day at Grand Canyon National Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Temperature can get really low during winter (high 10Fs, low 20Fs), especially at sunrise. Bring your winter cloth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Because of the elevation, the best view is ~10-15 mins after sunrise&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For sunset, it will be too late to get there at sunset because most of the light will be gone. Be there at least 30 mins before sunset&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For lodging, I stayed at one of the hotels inside the park. Next time, I would probably stay in Tusayan for better food and hotels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No LTE connection (AT&amp;amp;T) in most areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_lipan_point2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_sunrise.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><category term="Parks" /><summary type="html">A place that makes men humble</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crater Lake National Park Travel Guide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park-Travel-Guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crater Lake National Park Travel Guide" /><published>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park-Travel-Guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park-Travel-Guide/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Best to visit is summer due to snow and fog in other seasons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start your road trip from San Francisco and drive north on I-5&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Prepare to spend one day at Crater Lake National Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stay at the Crater Lake Lodge inside the park to save time from lining up at the park entrance&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t miss out the Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway nearby&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The main attraction is the Rim Village and the Scenic Rim Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is the deepest lake in the United States. At 1,943 feet, it is the second deepest in the Western Hemisphere and the ninth deepest in the world. Crater Lake is a recognized scenic wonder surrounded by rolling mountains, volcanic peaks and evergreen forests. It was formed when the volcano, Mount Mazama, collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are starting your road trip from San Francisco, I recommend you driving north on I-5 highway. The view along the way is incredible with snowy mountains and vast forests. You will gaze upon the second highest peak in the Cascade Range, Mount Shasta, soon after you enter Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/Mount%20Shasta.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Mount Shasta&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Mount Shasta

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can stop by Lake Siskiyou as a lunch stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the elevation (e.g. it is a volcano), there could be a lot of snow at the Crater Lake National Park during winter. Make sure to bring ice scrapper and warm cloth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/crater%20lake%20visitor%20center.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Crater Lake National Park Park Visitor Center&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Visitor Center at Crater Lake National Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The depth of Crater Lake gives it an incredible deep blue color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/crater%20lake%20national%20park.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Crater Lake

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/crater%20lake%20national%20park%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/crater%20lake%20national%20park%203.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fog is a challenge when visiting Crater Lake. When I visited the Park in May 2019, it was still snowing inside the park! And the fog was so dense that people could not see the lake even standing at the edge of the lake. I would recommend visiting in summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you enjoy the view at Crater Lake, don’t forget the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Volcanic_Legacy_Scenic_Byway&quot;&gt;Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway&lt;/a&gt; nearby. It is a quite and scenic drive dotted with cattle farms, beautiful lagoons, and national forests. I recommend driving at least a portion of it near Crater Lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/The%20Volcanic%20Legacy%20Scenic%20Byway%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/The%20Volcanic%20Legacy%20Scenic%20Byway%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      A farm on the Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/Umpqua%20National%20Forest.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Driving through Umpqua National Forest

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are heading back to San Francisco, you can take a detour to visit the Redwood National and States Parks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/Redwood%20National%20Park%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/Redwood%20National%20Park%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/Prairie%20Creek%20Redwoods%20State%20Park.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><category term="Parks" /><summary type="html">The deepest and purest lake in the United States</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mount Diablo State Park</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mount Diablo State Park" /><published>2019-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mount Diablo is one of the highest points in San Francisco Bay Area&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Best time to visit is spring when hills are green&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Limited parking at the summit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Diablo is one of the highest points in San Francisco Bay Area. It is a great hiking spot and you can even see Sierra Nevada on a clear day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can drive directly to the summit. However, the parking is extremely limited. I suggest go there in early morning or weekdays. The drive to the top is incredibly beautiful. Make sure to stop along the way and enjoy the views. Once you are the top, you have a 360 view of the bay area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/driving%20up%20mt%20diablo.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/mt%20diablo.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/mt%20diablo%20state%20park.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a clear day, you can barely see the Sierra Mountains (e.g. Yosemite).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/mt%20diablo%20facing%20Yosemite.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/mt%20diablo%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the wind farm in Birds Landing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/EDF%20windfarm.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="State Parks" /><category term="Parks" /><summary type="html">One of the tallest peak in San Francisco Bay Area</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Muri Woods Day Trip</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods-Day-Trip/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Muri Woods Day Trip" /><published>2018-12-29T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-12-29T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods-Day-Trip</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods-Day-Trip/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You need to reserve &lt;a href=&quot;https://gomuirwoods.com/&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; before visit&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plan to stay for 2 hours in the park&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muri Woods National Monument is named after the legendary John Muri who is often known as the “Father of National Parks”. One hundred fifty million years ago ancestors of redwood and sequoia trees grew throughout the United States. The logging industry practically destroyed these giant trees by the early 20th century. Today, Muri Woods National Monument, Redwoods National Park, and Sequoia National Park are the few places where we can still see these magnificent trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-visit&quot;&gt;The Visit&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muri Woods is fairly easy to visit. First, you need to reserve your ticket &lt;a href=&quot;https://gomuirwoods.com/&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;. Plan a couple of hours of complete the main trail. Once you arrive at the parking lot, it is fairly straightforward. The main trail is well paved and marked. There are four bridges that form the main trail. Typically, I recommend you start heading back at Bridge 4. Complete the loop and enjoy the gorgeous view of the redwood forests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_5.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_6.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_3.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_4.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><category term="Parks" /><summary type="html">A National Monument named after the 'Father of National Parks'</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Nikko Travel Guide</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Nikko-Travel-Guide/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nikko Travel Guide" /><published>2018-11-19T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-11-19T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Nikko-Travel-Guide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Nikko-Travel-Guide/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldritinerary&quot;&gt;TLDR/Itinerary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Must-do day trip if you are near Tokyo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plan a whole day to visit Shin-kyo -&amp;gt; Rinno-ji -&amp;gt; Tosho-gu -&amp;gt; Shoyo-en&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The best time to visit is during fall season when leaves start to change color&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nikko is a city one hour away from Tokyo. Nikko Tosho-gu (日光東照宮), a shrine built in 1617, is one of the 23 Japanese UNESCO World Heritage Sites. It is an easy spot to miss on your itinerary if you don’t know about it. Let’s not let that happen. Here is a complete guide to visit Nikko, Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;getting-there&quot;&gt;Getting there&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless you rent a car, there is really only one to get there: the JR East - Nikko Line. It runs about once every hour. So definitely plan your departure and don’t miss the last train home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;shin-kyo&quot;&gt;Shin-kyo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you arrive at the Nikko train station, start walking west towards Shin-kyo. You will already be impressed by the sights along the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/nikko1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shin-kyo translates to “The Sacred Bridge”. According to legend, a priest named Shōdō climbed Mt. Nantai in the year 766 to pray for national prosperity but could not cross the fast flowing Daiya River. Shōdō prayed and a 10 foot tall god named Jinja-Daiou appeared with two snakes twisted around his right arm. Jinja-Daiou released the blue and red snakes and they transformed themselves into a rainbow-like bridge covered with sedge, which Shōdō and his followers could use to cross the river. That is why this bridge is sometimes called Yamasugeno-jabashi, which means the “Snake Bridge of Sedge”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/Shinkyo%20Bridge.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;rinno-ji&quot;&gt;Rinno-ji&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After you cross “The Sacred Bridge”, start to explore the temple complex near Rinno-ji. This place is especially beautiful during fall. Nature has turned trees into canvas and leaves into colors. It was one of most amazing sight during my visit to Japan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/nikko2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/nikko3.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tosho-gu&quot;&gt;Tosho-gu&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/Tosho-gu.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tosho-gu was initially built in 1617 during the Edo period. Five structures at Nikkō Tōshō-gū are categorized as National Treasures of Japan, and three more as Important Cultural Properties. Famous buildings at the Tōshō-gū include the richly decorated Yōmeimon, a gate that is also known as “higurashi-no-mon”. The latter name means that one could look at it until sundown, and not tire of seeing it. Carvings in deep relief, painted in rich colors, decorate the surface of the structure. The next gate is the karamon decorated with white ornaments. Located nearby is a woodcarving of a sleepy cat, “Nemuri-neko”, attributed to Hidari Jingorō.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;shoyo-en&quot;&gt;Shoyo-en&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d be surprised if you are not impressed by the beauty of Nikko by now. Continue to explore the temple complex. One of the options is to walk towards Shoyo-en. Don’t rush it. Just take in the view and enjoy this moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/nikko/nikko4.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;final-thought&quot;&gt;Final Thought&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nikko is a must visit if you are near Tokyo. Carve out of one day in your itinerary and you won’t regret it!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="City" /><category term="Japan" /><summary type="html">A must visit UNESCO World Heritage Site near Tokyo</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">3 Days Travel Guide For Tokyo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/3-Days-Travel-Guide-for-Tokyo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3 Days Travel Guide For Tokyo" /><published>2018-11-18T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-11-18T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/3-Days-Travel-Guide-for-Tokyo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/3-Days-Travel-Guide-for-Tokyo/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldritinerary&quot;&gt;TLDR/Itinerary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 1: Hamarikyu Garden -&amp;gt; Tsukiji Fish Market -&amp;gt; Meiji Shrine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 2: The Imperial Palace East Gardens -&amp;gt; Asakusa&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 3: Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden -&amp;gt; Shibuya -&amp;gt; Akihabara&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spite of its close location to China and Korea, Japan is unlike any other east asian countries. Its unique culture, food, and people should be experienced by anyone with capable means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go to Japan, here is what you need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apply a tourist visa depending on your nationality&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Purchase a JR rail pass before you depart&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn some basic Japanese (more on language later)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bring your credit card with no foreign transaction fees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it is your first time visiting Japan, plan to visit multiple cities. During my first visit, I visited Tokyo, Nikko, Hakone, Kyoto, and Nara. In this guide, we will focus on Tokyo first. Visit my website for travel guides in other Japanese cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-airport&quot;&gt;The Airport&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After your long flight, you finally arrived at Japan! There are a few things that you need to do before heading out to your hotel though. First, exchange/validate your JR rail pass which allows you to get on most shinkansens (high speed rail). Next, purchase a Japanese sim card with a data plan at the airport. Lastly, you have to decide how to get to your hotels. One thing that many people don’t realize is how far away the Tokyo’s airport is to city center. There are three options to get to your hotel:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxi (very expensive, ~$200 USD)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Express train&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shuttle bus (~$10 USD)
Either train or bus is a good option to get to the city center and to your hotels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-1-hamarikyu-garden-tsukiji-fish-market-meiji-shrine&quot;&gt;Day 1 (Hamarikyu Garden, Tsukiji Fish Market, Meiji Shrine)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my first day in Tokyo to visit Hamarikyu Garden. It is a large park within the ultra-modern city dotted with lakes and traditional Japanese architectures. There aren’t many people there, especially on weekdays. You find a rare slice of peace and tranquility in this busy city. Plan to spend an entire morning in this beautiful park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu_Garden_1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Hamarikyu Garden

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu%20Garden%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu%20Garden%203.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After spending the morning walking around Hamarikyu Garden, you must be hungry! Lucky for you, the famous Tsukiji Fish Market is just nearby. Splurge yourself with fresh seafood and Japanese treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0030.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0032.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0035.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After indulging yourself at the Tsukiji Fish Market, head towards Meiji Shrine, one of the most popular shrines in Japan. While visiting the shrine, buy a shinto (small wooden plaque) and make a wish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Meiji%20Shrine%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Meiji%20Shrine%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-2-the-imperial-palace-east-gardens-asakusa&quot;&gt;Day 2 (The Imperial Palace East Gardens, Asakusa)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the first day in Tokyo, you must be excited right? I recommend a lightweight schedule for day 2 to relax and explore the city.
I started my day 2 in Tokyo at The Imperial Palace East Gardens. I have to say it is a lot less impressive than Hamarikyu or Meiji Shrine. Next, you can visit Asakusa, the famous temple district with lots of touristy shops. There were so many people when I visited! It is a popular spot with both tourists and locals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Asakusa.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out the cute little shops in this district. Also, one of the conveyor belt sushi restaurants nearby is really good. So much better than what we have outside of Japan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Asakusa2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-3-shinjuku-gyoen-national-garden-shibuya-akihabara&quot;&gt;Day 3 (Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden, Shibuya, Akihabara)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Day 3, I started the morning by going to Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden which was a residence of Lord Naito.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Shinjuku%20Gyo-en.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, start walking your way to Shibuya. Along the way, you will encounter Takeshita Street, a pedestrian shopping street lined with fashion boutiques, cafes, and restaurants. The famous Dominique Ansel’s bakery is just nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Dominique%20Ansel%20Tokyo%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Dominique%20Ansel%20Tokyo%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended the night at Akihabara, the center of Japan’s anime and manga culture. Whether you are looking for cute office supplies, manga, or mecha models, you can find them at Akihabara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-end&quot;&gt;The End&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are so much more to explore in Tokyo. The little alleys, the ramen shops, or the Michelin Star restaurants all beg me to return. And I am sure I will. Hopefully you will too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="City" /><category term="Japan" /><summary type="html">The mythical capital of the Far-east nation</summary></entry></feed>