<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-04-04T20:37:31-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">422parks.com</title><subtitle>Travel guide to National Parks with landscape photos</subtitle><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><entry><title type="html">Grand Canyon National Park</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Grand-Canyon-National-Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grand Canyon National Park" /><published>2020-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-11-28T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Grand-Canyon-National-Park</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Grand-Canyon-National-Park/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-day-itinerary&quot;&gt;1 Day Itinerary&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scenic Option (e.g. photos, easy trail):
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Watch sunrise at Mather Point&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Walk the Rim Trail between Marther Point and Yavapai Point&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Lunch break&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Drive the Desert View Drive to visit different vistas (afternoon)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Watch the sunset at Yavapai Point or Pipe Creek Vista&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Outdoor Option (e.g. trail, exercise):
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Bright Angel Trail&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-day-itineray&quot;&gt;2 Day Itineray&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Watch sunsrise at Yavapai Point&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Complete the other option (scenic or outdoor)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lunch break&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the shuttle bus to Hermits Rest&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Grand Canyonis a unique place to visit. It is a place that makes men humble. It is a place that displays the grandeur of nature. It is a place that everyone should visit at least once in their lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_mather_point.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Sunrise at Mather Point&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Sunrise at Mather Point

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the must-do activities is to watch the sunrise at the Grand Canyon National Park. It is a magic moment. The tips of the cliffs start to glow. As the sun rises, more and more of the canyon bathes in the orange light. The best locations to view sunrise are &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yaki Point&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Hopi Point&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you enjoy the sunrise at &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, walk towards &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;. It is an easy walk with paved trail. With the sun behind you, you get to see the fully glory of the Grand Canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since you get up early to see the sunrise, you probably wake up early. Rest or take a nap. You can grab lunch at the General Store in &lt;strong&gt;Grand Canyon Market Plaza&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you visit Grand Canyon, don’t miss out the &lt;strong&gt;Desert View Drive&lt;/strong&gt;. Although Mather Point and Yavapai Point are the most convienient, there are plenty of unique view points along Desert View Drive. The best of them is &lt;strong&gt;Lipan Point&lt;/strong&gt;. You can see how the Colorado River has carved down the earth to form the Grand Canyon, of which you wouldn’t see from Mather or Yavapai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_lipan_point.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Lipan Point&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Lipan Point

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are staying the night, don’t miss out on the sunset. The best places to watch sunset are &lt;strong&gt;Lipan Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Mather Point&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Yavapai Point&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Hopi Point&lt;/strong&gt;. This will conclude your day at the Grand Canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have one more day at Grand Canyon, head to the &lt;strong&gt;Bright Angel Trailhead&lt;/strong&gt; on the next morning. Be sure to go there early as parking spots are limited. Bright Angel Trail takes you to the bottom of the canyon. Did I mention that Grand Canyon is one mile deep on average? It is a challenging trail for the average person. Depending on your conditions, you should decide when to head back. Remember, it takes twice as much time to climb up then to go down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Depending on how far down you go on the Bright Angel Trail, it can take you an entire day. If you have time left, visit the west side of the South Rim. Take the shuttle bus to &lt;strong&gt;Hermits Rest&lt;/strong&gt; or walk the trail. You can appreciate how deep the Canyon is on your way to &lt;strong&gt;Trailview Overlook&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;final-thoughts&quot;&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not sure words can describe the beauty of Grand Canyon. You have to go there to see it and experience it youself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For most people, it is probably enough to stay two nights and one day at Grand Canyon National Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Temperature can get really low during winter (high 10Fs, low 20Fs), especially at sunrise. Bring your winter cloth&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Because of the elevation, the best view is ~10-15 mins after sunrise&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For sunset, it will be too late to get there at sunset because most of the light will be gone. Be there at least 30 mins before sunset&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For lodging, I stayed at one of the hotels inside the park. Next time, I would probably stay in Tusayan for better food and hotels.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;No LTE connection (AT&amp;amp;T) in most areas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_lipan_point2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon_sunrise.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/grand_canyon/grand_canyon2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><summary type="html">The Grand Canyon, one of the most grandeur places on Earth, is a unique place to visit. It is unlike any other places that I have been to.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Crater Lake National Park</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Crater Lake National Park" /><published>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-05-26T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Crater-Lake-National-Park/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Best to visit is summer due to snow and fog in other seasons&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Start your roadmap from San Francisco and drive north on I-5&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Prepare to spend one day at Crater Lake National Park&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Stay at the Crater Lake Lodge inside the park to save time from lining up at the park entrance&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Don’t miss out the Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway nearby&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The main atrraction is the Rim Village and the Scenic Rim Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crater Lake is the deepest lake in the United States. At 1,943 feet, it is the second deepest in the Western Hemisphere and the ninth deepest in the world. Crater Lake is a recognized scenic wonder surrounded by rolling mountains, volcanic peaks and evergreen forests. It was formed when the volcano, Mount Mazama, collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are starting your roadtrip from San Francisco, I recommend you driving north on I-5 highway. The view along the way is incredible with snowy mountains and vast forests. You will gaze upon the second highest peak in the Cascade Range, Mount Shasta, soon after you enter Oregon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02560-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Mt Shasta&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Mt Shasta

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can stop by Lake Siskiyou as a lunch stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the elevation (e.g. it is a volcano), there could be a lot of snow at the Craker Lake National Park during winter. Make sure to bring ice scrapper and warm cloth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/crater%20lake%20visitor%20center.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Visitor Center at Crater Lake National Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The depth of Crater Lake gives it an incredible deep blue color.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02606-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Crater Lake

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02611-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02694-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fog is a challenge when visiting Crater Lake. When I visited the Park in May 2019, it was still snowing inside the park! And the fog was so dense that people could not see the lake even standing at the edge of the lake. I would recommend visiting in summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you enjoy the view at Crater Lake, don’t forget the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Volcanic_Legacy_Scenic_Byway&quot;&gt;Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway&lt;/a&gt; nearby. It is a quite and scenic drive dotted with cattle farms, beautiful lagoons, and national forests. I recommend driving at least a portion of it near Crater Lake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/The%20Volcanic%20Legacy%20Scenic%20Byway%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/The%20Volcanic%20Legacy%20Scenic%20Byway%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      A farm on the Volcanic Legacy Scenic Byway

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02605-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Driving through Umpqua National Forest

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are heading back to San Francisco, you can take a detour to visit the Redwood National and States Parks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02872-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02882-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/crater/DSC02891-Edit.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><summary type="html">Crater Lake is the deepest lake in the United States. It is a recognized scenic wonder surrounded by rolling mountains, volcanic peaks and evergreen forests.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mount Diablo State Park</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mount Diablo State Park" /><published>2019-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-03-19T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Mount-Diablo-State-Park/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mount Diablo is one of the highest points in San Francisco Bay Area&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Best time to visit is spring when hills are green&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Limited parking at the summit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mount Diablo is one of the highest points in San Francisco Bay Area. It is a great hiking spot and you can even see Sierra Nevada on a clear day!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can drive directly to the summit. However, the parking is extremely limited. I suggest go there in early morning or weekdays. The drive to the top is incredbly beautiful. Make sure to stop along the way and enjoy the views. Once you are the top, you have a 360 view of the bay area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02269.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02308.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02281.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a clear day, you can barely see the Sierra Mountains (e.g. Yosemite).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02286.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02293.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the wind farm in Birds Landing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/mt_diablo/DSC02300.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="State Parks" /><summary type="html">One of the tallest peak in San Francisco Bay Area</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Muri Woods</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Muri Woods" /><published>2018-12-29T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-12-29T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Muri-Woods/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldr&quot;&gt;TLDR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You need to reserve &lt;a href=&quot;https://gomuirwoods.com/&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt; before visit&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Plan to stay for 2 hours in the park&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muri Woods National Monument is named after the legendary John Muri who is often known as the “Father of National Parks”. One hundred fifty million years ago ancestors of redwood and sequoia trees grew throughout the United States. The logging industry practically destroyed these giant trees by the early 20th century. Today, Muri Woods National Monument, Redwoods National Park, and Sequoia National Park are the few places where we can still see these magnificient trees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Muri Woods is fairly easy to visit. Reserve your ticket &lt;a href=&quot;https://gomuirwoods.com/&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;, drive to the park lot, and there you go. Trails are well marked and easy to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_5.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_6.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_3.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/muri/muri_wood_4.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="National Parks" /><summary type="html">One hundred fifty million years ago ancestors of redwood and sequoia trees grew throughout the United States. Today, Muri Wood National Monument is one of the few places to see the magnificient redwood.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tokyo</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Tokyo/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tokyo" /><published>2018-11-18T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-11-18T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Tokyo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Tokyo/">&lt;h1 id=&quot;tldritinary&quot;&gt;TLDR/Itinary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 1: Hamarikyu Garden -&amp;gt; Tsukiji Fish Market -&amp;gt; Meiji Shrine&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 2: The Imperial Palace East Gardens -&amp;gt; Asakusa&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Day 3: Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden -&amp;gt; Shibuya -&amp;gt; Akihabara&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In spite of its close location to China and Korea, Japan is unlike any other east asian countries. Its unique culture, food, and people should be experienced by anyone with capable means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go to Japan, here is what you need:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Apply a tourist visa depending on your nationality&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Purchase a JR rail pass before you depart&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Learn some basic Japanese (more on language later)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bring your credit card with no foreign transaction fees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If it is your first time visiting Japan, plan to visit multiple cities. During my first visit, I visited Tokyto, Nikko, Hakone, Kyoto, and Nara. In this guide, we will focus on Tokyto first. Visit my website for travel guides in other Japanese cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-diary&quot;&gt;The Diary&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-airport&quot;&gt;The Airport&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After your long flight, you finanlly arrived at Japan! There are a few things that you need to do before heading out to your hotel though. First, exchange/validate your JR rail pass which allows you to get on most shinkansens (high speed rail). Next, purchase a Japanese sim card with a data plan at the airport. Lastly, you have to decide how to get to your hotels. One thing that many people don’t realize is how far away the Tokyo’s airport is to city center. There are three options to get to your hotel:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taxi (very expensive, ~$200 USD)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Express train&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shuttle bus (~$10 USD)
Either train or bus is a good option to get to the city center and to your hotels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-1-hamarikyu-garden-tsukiji-fish-market-meiji-shrine&quot;&gt;Day 1 (Hamarikyu Garden, Tsukiji Fish Market, Meiji Shrine)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started my first day in Tokyo to visit Hamarikyu Garden. It is a large park within the ultra-modern city dotted with lakes and tranditional Japanese architectures. There aren’t many people there, especially on weekdays. You find a rare slice of peace and tranqulity in this busy city. Plan to spend an entire morning in this beautiful park.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu_Garden_1.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
      Hamarikyu Garden

    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu%20Garden%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Hamarikyu%20Garden%203.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After spending the morning walking around Hamarikyu Garden, you must be hungry! Lucky for you, the famous Tsukiji Fish Market is just nearby. Splurge yourself with fresh seafood and Japanese treats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0030.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0032.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/IMG_0035.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After indulging yourself at the Tsukiji Fish Market, head towards Meiji Shrine, one of the most popular shrines in Japan. While visiting the shrine, buy a shinto (small wooden plaque) and make a wish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Meiji%20Shrine%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Meiji%20Shrine%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-2-the-imperial-palace-east-gardens-asakusa&quot;&gt;Day 2 (The Imperial Palace East Gardens, Asakusa)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the first day in Tokyo, you must be excited right? I recommend a lightweight schedule for day 2 to relax and explore the city.
I started my day 2 in Tokyto at The Imperial Palace East Gardens. I have to say it is a lot less impressive than Hamarikyu or Meiji Shrine. Next, you can visit Asakusa, the famous temple district with lots of touristty shops. There were so many people when I visited! It is a popular spot with both tourists and locals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Asakusa.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss out the cute little shops in this district. Also, one of the conveyor belt sushi restaurants nearby is really good. So much better than what we have outside of Japan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Asakusa2.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;day-3-shinjuku-gyoen-national-garden-shibuya-akihabara&quot;&gt;Day 3 (Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden, Shibuya, Akihabara)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Day 3, I started the morning by going to Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden which was a residence of Lord Naito.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Shinjuku%20Gyo-en.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, start walking your way to Shibuya. Along the way, you will encounter Takeshita Street, a pedestrain shopping street lined with fashion boutiques, cafes, and resturations. The famous Dominique Ansel’s bakery is just nearby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half &quot;&gt;
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Dominique%20Ansel%20Tokyo%201.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
    
      &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/japan/tokyo/Dominique%20Ansel%20Tokyo%202.webp&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
    
  
  
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I ended the night at Akihabara, the center of Japan’s anime and manga culture. Whether you are looking for cute office supplies, mangas, or mecha models, you can find them at Akihabara.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-end&quot;&gt;The End&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are so much more to explore in Tokyo. The little alleys, the ramen shops, or the Michelin Star resturants all beg me to return. And I am sure I will. Hopefully you will too.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kevin Takahashi</name></author><category term="City" /><category term="Japan" /><summary type="html">The mythical capital of the Far-east nation</summary></entry></feed>